this is the patriot missile system
这是爱国者导弹系统
and we can divide it into ten basic parts
我们可以把它分成十个基本部分
as shown here with all the interiors
如这里所示，所有的内饰
revealing its complex parts and systems
揭示其复杂的部件和系统
it also has these small thrusters or short
它也有这些小推进器或短推进器
propellant motors that fire explosively to
爆炸的推进剂发动机
refine the missile's trajectory to its target
使导弹的弹道精确到目标
we'll also be diving into the step by
我们也将潜入一步一步
step process of how this works
这是如何工作的步骤过程
the missile system
导弹系统
and the basic comparison between the
和之间的基本比较
s-400 and the patriot missile
S-400和爱国者导弹
in the pros and cons sections to
在利弊部分
help us understand it better
帮助我们更好地理解它
so stay tuned and don't miss a beat
所以请继续关注，不要错过任何一个节拍
the m i m one o four patriot is a
m i m one o 4爱国者是一个
surface to air missile Sam system
地空导弹萨姆系统
the primary of its kind used by the United States
美国使用的同类产品中的主要产品
army and several allied Nations
军队和几个盟国
and with the most advanced technology
并采用最先进的技术
comparing to the s four hundred missile
与四百枚导弹相比
for a patriot battery it cost an
对于爱国者电池，它的成本是
astronomical one billion dollars
天文数字的十亿美元
while a single missile cost four million us dollars
而一枚导弹要花费四百万美元
comparing to the s-400 it cost five hundred
与s-400相比，它的价格是500英镑。
million dollars for a single battery mobile
单节电池手机价值100万美元
long ranged surface to air missile system
远程地空导弹系统
the patriot is made up of six basic parts
爱国者由六个基本部分组成
number one engagement control station
一号交战控制站
this is the fire direction center for patriot firing
这是爱国者射击的射击指挥中心
battery operations and is the only manned station
电池运行，是唯一的载人站
in the firing battery during the air battle
在空战期间的发射炮台中
number two electric power plant
第二发电厂
this is electric power for operation of the
这是操作的电力
fire control section also called app
消防部门也称为应用程序
number three radar set
三号雷达装置
this is a multifunction phased array
这是一个多功能相控阵
radar mounted on a semi trailer
装在半挂车上的雷达
number four antenna Mast group
四号天线桅杆组
this provides mobile quick erect antennas and
这提供了移动快速直立天线和
amplifiers for ultra high frequency Communications
超高频通信放大器
number five launching station
五号发射站
this is a remotely operated self
这是一个远程操作的自我
contained unit with its own power plant
带有自己的发电厂的封闭单元
can fire up to four patriot guided
最多可以发射四个爱国者引导
missiles at designated targets  number six
导弹瞄准6号目标
the Patriot guided missile m i m one o four is wingless
爱国者导弹m i m 1 o 4是无翼的
it does however have four tail control fins and is
然而，它确实有四个尾部控制鳍，并且是
propelled in flight by a single stage solid propellant
由单级固体推进剂推动飞行
rocket motor
火箭发动机
now let's look in more detail at each of the parts
现在让我们更详细地看看每个部分
before we move into the step by step process
在我们进入逐步过程之前
this is the engagement control station and can control
这是交战控制站，可以控制
up to eight launching stations through these VHF
通过这些甚高频发射多达8个发射台
radio data links and are located above the truck
无线电数据链路，位于卡车上方
this is the main station number one
这里是一号总站
followed by main station two
其次是二号总站
and last one is the main station number three
最后一个是三号总站
electric power plant
发电厂
it consists of two one hundred fifty kilowatt turbine
它由两百五十千瓦的涡轮机组成
generators mounted on a five ton truck chassis
安装在5吨卡车底盘上的发电机
these generators operate primarily on diesel
这些发电机主要使用柴油
fuel but have a multi fuel capability
燃料，但具有多种燃料能力
the electric power plant is connected to
发电厂连接到
the radar set by three power cables
三根电源线设置的雷达
while the engagement control station is
而交战控制站
connected by a power cable and a control cable
由电源线和控制线连接
radar set  this is the radar set
雷达组这是雷达组
and interestingly it does not rotate
有趣的是，它不旋转。
let's look closely at its parts
让我们仔细看看它的各个部分
this is the main array
这是主阵列
moving down is theIFF or friend or foe antenna
向下移动是IFF或朋友或敌人的天线
this is the tvn array or in full form track via missile
这是tvn阵列或通过导弹的完整形式轨道
moving ahead is the antenna lens assembly
前面是天线透镜组件
once in place
一旦到位
the raider's phased array radar antenna is elevated and
突袭机的相控阵雷达天线升高
locked at a sixty seven point five degree angle
锁定在六十七点五度角
antenna Mast group
天线桅杆组
this is the antenna Mast group's protective cover
这是天线桅杆组的保护套
the antenna masts extend to a maximum height of one
天线桅杆延伸到最大高度为1
hundred feet eleven inches from ground level
离地面一百英尺十一英寸
just like this animation
就像这个动画
the antenna Mast group provides ultra high frequency
天线桅杆组提供超高频
Communications required for the engagement control station
交战控制站所需的通信
this launching platform is made up of three parts
这个发射平台由三部分组成
this is dlf antenna in full form the distributed
这是完整形式的分布式dlf天线
Ledger technology responsible for continuously sharing
Ledger技术负责持续共享
data directly to the engagement control station
数据直接发送到交战控制站
this is the canister and inside it
这是罐子，在里面
houses four pack three missiles
房子四包三导弹
moving forward we have the electrical
向前看，我们有电气
power unit that powers the launchers
为发射器供电的动力装置
this is the patriot missile
这是爱国者导弹
so let us look at what's inside it
让我们看看里面有什么
this is the fuse silica蕊筒
这是保险丝硅石蕊筒
moving to the back is the seeker assembly
移到后面的是探索者组件
this is the terminal guidance package
这是终端引导包
most probably contains the gps of the patriot missile
很可能包含爱国者导弹的GPS
just behind it is the modular
就在它后面是模块化的
midcourse package navigation subsystem
中途包导航子系统
this is the warhead and weighs around ninety kilogram
这是弹头，重约90公斤
responsible for destroying the enemy projectiles
负责摧毁敌方炮弹
this is the inertial sensor electronics
这是惯性传感器电子设备
along with the gyro acceleration assembly
还有陀螺仪加速组件
moving ahead is a propulsion
前进是一种推动力
arming and firing unit which we will
武装和发射单位，我们将
explain further in the video ahead
在前面的视频中进一步解释
this is a propellant section and takes up
这是一个推进剂部分
around forty percent of the missile's space
导弹大约40%的空间
it is basically a solid fuel for the missile
它基本上是导弹的固体燃料
just behind the propellant is the motor pump and
推进剂后面是发动机泵和
actuator and the last section of the missile is
执行器，导弹的最后一部分是
the fins that help steer the missile
帮助操纵导弹的鳍
it weighs around three hundred and seventeen
它重约三百一十七磅
kilograms or six hundred and ninety eight pounds
千克或六百九十八磅
it is approximately five point one meters long and has a
它大约有五点一米长，有一个
diameter of two hundred and fifty four millimeters
直径二百五十四毫米
let's compare this to a person to
让我们把这个比作一个人
understand its size visually
直观地理解它的大小
now that we established the basic missile system
现在我们建立了基本的导弹系统
let's look at the step by step
让我们一步一步地看
process of how this is launched
如何启动的过程
step number one
第一步
multiple patriot missiles will be deployed
将部署多枚爱国者导弹
to provide overlapping missile coverage
提供重叠的导弹覆盖
step number two
第二步
the radar electronically scans the sky searching the
雷达以电子方式扫描天空
entire horizon with overlapping pencil beam
整个地平线与重叠的铅笔光束
step number three
第三步
let's take two targets to help us visualize
让我们选择两个目标来帮助我们想象
an intercontinental ballistic missile
洲际弹道导弹
fired by the enemy from the horizon
被敌人从地平线上发射
and a low flying cruise missile like this
还有像这样低空飞行的巡航导弹
one approaching near the frontlines
一个接近前线
step number four
第四步
when the target is detected
当检测到目标时
the radar communicates with the computer
雷达与计算机通信
in the engagement control station
在交战控制站
step number five
第五步
targets can be tracked manually or
可以手动跟踪目标或
automatically and change the designation from
自动并更改名称
hostile to friendly if and when appropriate
在适当的时候敌视友好
step number six
第六步
the engagement control station then gives the command
然后交战控制站发出命令
to the launching station with the required data
带着所需的数据去发射站
step number seven as per operational doctrine any
第七步根据作战原则
engagement requires two pack three missiles to
交战需要两包三枚导弹
increase the probability of the hit ratio
提高命中率的概率
step number eight the missile in the early
第八步导弹在早期
stages uses inertial guidance specified to
级使用指定为
launch from the engagement control station
从交战控制站发射
step number nine
第九步
just shortly before arrival at the intercept point
就在到达拦截点前不久
the missile uses the ka band seeker to track the target
导弹使用ka波段导引头跟踪目标
an optimal aim point is selected and
选择最佳瞄准点并
terminal guidance is initiated
终端引导启动
step number ten
第十步
the short propellant motors fires explosively to
短推进剂发动机爆炸
refine the missile trajectory to its target
将导弹弹道精确到目标
this helps the missile to reach its point of trajectory and
这有助于导弹到达其弹道点
enables the missile a hit to kill intercept of the target
使导弹命中目标并拦截目标
direct body to body contact with the missile creates very
直接身体接触导弹会造成非常
high energy which helps destroy weapons of mass destruction
有助于摧毁大规模杀伤性武器的高能
once the threat has been destroyed
一旦威胁被摧毁
the remaining pack three missiles will be
剩下的三包导弹将
terminated by the engagement control station
由交战控制站终止
let's simplify it even better  number one
让我们简化它，更好地第一
radar sweeps the sky for threats
雷达扫描天空中的威胁
number two sends data to control station
二号向控制站发送数据
number three
三号
launchers fire the missile
发射器发射导弹
number four  pac three missiles are guided to the
四号pac三号导弹被引导到
target by the engagement control station
交战控制站的目标
let's look at the pros and cons of this missile
让我们来看看这枚导弹的利弊
the patriot missile system can detect and
爱国者导弹系统可以探测和
respond to incoming missiles within seconds
在数秒内对来袭的导弹作出反应
which is essential in defending against surprise attacks
这对防御突然袭击至关重要
the patriot missile system can be
爱国者导弹系统可以
integrated with other defense systems
与其他防御系统集成
such as radar and fighter jets
比如雷达和战斗机
to provide a comprehensive defense network
提供全面的防御网络
let's look at the cons
让我们看看缺点
the deployment time for the s-400
s-400的部署时间
missile defense system is five minutes
导弹防御系统还有五分钟
while for the patriot missile defense
而爱国者导弹防御系统
system it is twenty five minutes or more
系统是25分钟或更长时间
its Radar is a detection to kill system
它的雷达是一种侦察杀伤系统
meaning a single unit performs all search
意味着单个单元执行所有搜索
identification
鉴定
track and engagement functions
跟踪和参与功能
the s four hundred has around three or four radars
s400有大约三四个雷达
the big bird long range Radar
大鸟远程雷达
the gravestone fire control Radar
墓碑火控雷达
the all altitude radar
全高度雷达
and the last one is the mobile mast radar system
最后一个是移动式桅杆雷达系统
we create original 3d animation from scratch
我们从头开始创建原创3d动画
so please like and subscribe to help us
所以请喜欢并订阅以帮助我们
create better animation for years to come
为未来创造更好的动画